Guide to the Gary Hallinen papers, 1971-1991
Hallinen, Gary papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Gary Hallinen papers, 1971-1991
7804
Hallinen, Gary
.3 cubic feet
Correspondence, organizational records, printed materials and memorabilia.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Files belonging to Gary Hallinen from various gay rights organizations including the Gay Liberation Front, GALS, and the Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files belonging to Gary Hallinen from various gay rights organizations including the Gay Liberation Front, GALS, and the Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley. These include meeting minutes, correspondence, articles of incorporation, administrative files as well as posters and pamphlets.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Hallinen, Gary
Subjects:
Gay men -- Societies and clubs -- New York (State).
Places:
New York (State) -- Rochester
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records
NOTES
Arrangement and description of the Gary Hallinen papers, #7804 made possible in part by a grant from the Documentary Heritage Program of the New York State Archives, a program of the State Education Department
CONTAINER LIST
- Meeting notes and minutes, 1971-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  For Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley, GALS, Gay Liberation Front and other gay related groups. Also includes some correspondence
- Housing Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Executive Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Administrative (1), 1981, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Articles of incorporation materials, GAGV constitution and amendments, policies and budget materials
- Donor and Board Member Lists, c. 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Administrative (2), 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Includes a GAGV Mission Statement, correspondence, meeting minutes, fliers, financial information and newsletters
- NAMES Project - Quilt Committee, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Administrative (3), 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Includes news clippings, correspondence, budget and financial information and committee meeting minutes and agendas.
- GAGV Gala Auction, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- GAGV Convention, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Information pamphlets and flyers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)